Stay in the middle
Like you a little
Don't want no riddle
말해줘 Say it back
oh, say it ditto
아침은 너무 멀어
so say it ditto
훌쩍 커버렸어
함께한 기억처럼
널 보는 내 마음은
어느새 여름 지나 가을
기다렸지
All this time
Do you want somebody
Like I want somebody
날 보고 웃었지만
Do you think about me now
Yeah, all the time
내 길었던 하루
난 보고 싶어
Ra-ta-ta-ta 울린 심장
I got nothing to lose
널 좋아한다고
Ra-ta-ta-ta 울린 심장
But I don't want to
Stay in the middle
Like you a little
Don't want no riddle
말해줘 Say it back
Oh say it ditto
아침은 너무 멀어
so say it ditto
I don't want to
Walk in this 미로
다 아는 건 아니어도
바라던 대로
말해줘 Say it back
Oh say it ditto
I want you so want you so
Say it ditto
Say it did I
I want you so want you so
I want you so want you so say it did I
저를 상상했지
항상 나 있던
처음 느낌 그대로 난
היה 먹던 시작의 느낌 그대로 난
기다렸지 기다렸지
All this time
I got nothing to lose
널 좋아한다고
다다다단 울린 심장
But I don't want to
So I can break
Stay in the middle
Like you a little
I don't want to
Walk in this middle
다 아는 건 아니어도 바라던 대로
말해줘 Say it back